{
    "id": "bc45133d528e441d905a5846eb176051",
    "title": "Idioms Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "A cock and bull story is ……………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a foolish, unbelievable story",
                "a dead letter",
                "an epic"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2dbe9ec3e75d478c8600e784e1307962"
        },
        {
            "question": "Training is …………………… .. to a doctor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "inseparable",
                "indispensable",
                "irrefutable"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9f9edd254b424b4e9a9484e02584f45e"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is a website for students …………………… . mother language is not English.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "whose",
                "of whom"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ea328b03040245039e256595ddc34b41"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I asked them who took the money, the boys ……………………… ignorance.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "affected",
                "effected",
                "acted"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0a12d861e7354bc79460c1f2b395f5f7"
        },
        {
            "question": "A good manager should …………………… . from criticizing his subordinates.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "abstain",
                "refrain",
                "avoid"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9f6c9bd79182423ea6a4971654fce415"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was an ………………… in the murder.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "accomplice",
                "accessary",
                "accessory"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1b9061964de14311af0f95b020f10e8c"
        },
        {
            "question": "When people ………………… . ill, they consult their doctor hoping to get the best medical care.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "turn",
                "go",
                "fall"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "eb0e83cb2f094daaac2991f8b2267ac5"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is Mrs. Seth …………………… . they say is the best pianist in the town.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f81af6fe0e9b465ebcfd6989fdbc979a"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is high time she ………………… . the dues.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "pay",
                "pays",
                "paid",
                "has paid"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "dd1fa929902943b5b05d97024a522774"
        },
        {
            "question": "He tiptoed into the room lest he …………………. the baby.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wake up",
                "should wake up",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e47e7f8400ba4b1db97dd4279120c634"
        }
    ]
}